[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ana.webp",
    "match": 17
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ftayza.webp",
    "match": 18
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/maria.webp",
    "match": 19
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/brahim.webp",
    "match": 20
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/lhindi.webp",
    "match": 21
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/reda.webp",
    "match": 22
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ilyas.webp",
    "match": 23
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ilias.webp",
    "match": 24
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/amine.webp",
    "match": 16
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/bsar.webp",
    "match": 15
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/hamid.webp",
    "match": 14
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/abdelhadi.webp",
    "match": 13
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/abdelhadi.webp",
    "match": 12
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/hamid.webp",
    "match": 11
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/bsar.webp",
    "match": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/amine.webp",
    "match": 9
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ana.webp",
    "match": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ftayza.webp",
    "match": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/maria.webp",
    "match": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/brahim.webp",
    "match": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/lhindi.webp",
    "match": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/reda.webp",
    "match": 6
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ilyas.webp",
    "match": 7
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "front": "../images/front.webp",
    "back": "../images/ilias.webp",
    "match": 8
  }
]